<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Mohammed-Sunasra</title>
 <link href="https://mohammed-sunasra.github.io//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="https://mohammed-sunasra.github.io//"/>
 <updated>2022-08-23T18:07:23+05:30</updated>
 <id>https://mohammed-sunasra.github.io/</id>
 <author>
   <name>Mohammed Sunasra</name>
   <email>sunasramohd@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Getting started!</title>
   <link href="https://mohammed-sunasra.github.io//2022/08/19/hello-world/"/>
   <updated>2022-08-19T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>https://mohammed-sunasra.github.io//2022/08/19/hello-world</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;overview&quot;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello there! Welcome to my blog. I am a tech enthusiast currently building Pixeldust and working as an all-around engineer in the areas of Backend Development, MLOPs, Machine learning, and also a bit on DevOps. If you wish to find more about me or contact me, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;/about/&quot;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot;&gt;Contact&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I have always pondered upon the idea of starting a tech blog for the past few years, I found myself too busy either building stuff or learning new skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am currently at a stage where I get to try out a lot of new stuff in tech(languages, tools, frameworks) and always wanted to document my understanding.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;topics&quot;&gt;Topics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You would find me posting about things like Programming(in general), Django, REST APIs, Docker, Kubernetes, Podcasts, or life experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of the posts in this blog would be like notes, so I’ll revisit them, add more content or change something here and there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main purpose of this blog is to keep things as a living document that I can use to teach others and also re-learn things in the future to refresh my memory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excited to start doing what I always wanted and would try my best to explain things in a way people can benefit from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thank you,&lt;/strong&gt;
:heart:&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
